puma.com 2018-09-10

# Sites-NA-Site

## Customer Service

## Privacy Policy

* * *

PUMA (collectively, “PUMA” or "we", "us", or "our") respects the privacy of all of our visitors and pledges to provide you with the best online experience possible. This PUMA Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes what information we collect from you, how we may use it and the steps we take to ensure that it is protected. This Privacy Policy also applies to information we may collect from you through any PUMA retail store, PUMA sponsored events, and through official surveys and sweepstakes entry forms, or in any other instance when you contact us. **BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE, MOBILE APPLICATION OR OTHER PUMA PRODUCT OR SERVICE ON ANY COMPUTER, MOBILE PHONE, TABLET, CONSOLE OR OTHER DEVICE (COLLECTIVELY, "DEVICE"), YOU CONSENT TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. PUMA** may modify this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting. Your continued use of our products and services constitutes your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and any updates. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is subject to, the [_Terms of Use_](https://us.puma.com/en/us/terms-and-conditions/TERMS_AND_CONDITIONS.html "Terms of Use").

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information you give us or permit us to access. Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, image, birth date, email and physical address, IP address, telephone number or mobile phone identifier, gender, contact lists, social media information, location (including GPS) information, activity and performance information, and when necessary, credit card information. We also collect information about gift and e-giftcard recipients provided by the giver. 

We may also collect information regarding your interaction with, and use of, our products and services. Information we may collect includes, but is not limited to, your telephone number, Device identifier and hardware information, IP address, browser type and language, cookie information, system type, whether you have enabling software to access certain features, access times, referring website URLs, information about your purchases and other information about your interactions with us.

We may combine information you give us with other information from PUMA sources, transactions and communications. This may include, but is not limited to, information from PUMA retail stores, direct mail, catalogs, events, products and applications, or other PUMA interactions. We may also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data from third parties. 

### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

We may use cookies and other collection tools, such as clickstream data and web beacons, to gather information about your visits on our website so we can enhance your experience. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us, which will enable us to analyze and better customize your visits. 

What Are Cookies? Cookies are data files stored within your browser when you interact with a website. These data files allow the website to recall important information about your visit, help better understand your preferences and improve your overall experience.

You may limit or turn off cookies and other collection tools by adjusting your browner settings. If you turn off certain collection tools, you may not have access to many features that make your experience more efficient and some of our services and features may not function properly. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so we can offer you a better shopping experience on our sites.

We also work with other companies who use tracking technologies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. For example, we use Google Analytics and Adobe SiteCatalyst on the website to analyze how users use the website and to provide advertisements to you on other websites. For more information about how to opt-out of having your information used by Google Analytics, visit [_https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). For more information about how to opt-out of having your information used by Adobe SiteCatalyst, visit [_http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html_](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html). These companies may not recognize or respond to browser “Do Not Track” signals. For more information about third party cookies, including information about how to opt-out of these technologies, visit _www.aboutads.info/choices_ (US) or [_http://youradchoices.ca/choices_](http://youradchoices.ca/choices) (Canada). We do not operate or control these sites, and are not responsible for the opt-out choices available there.

### USE OF INFORMATION

We may use your information to provide products and services to you including:  

  * Enhancing, personalizing and customizing user experiences, such as placing an order and other activities
  * Communicating with you about your purchase, account information or customer service
  * Analyzing user behavior and trends to better understand our customers and gain consumer insights
  * Providing and conducting marketing and promotions
  * Communicating with you about our products, services and events, and for other promotional purposes
  * Administering contests, promotions, events, surveys or other features 
  * Displaying relevant marketing to you and other information about PUMA

We only send you communications if you have opted-in to receive PUMA e-mails and/or SMS messages. If you no longer want to receive emails/SMS messages or want to delete/update your personal data, please visit the [_My Account_](https://us.puma.com/en/us/account) page.

### PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

PUMA uses technical and organizational measures designed to protect your information against unauthorized access, theft, and loss. While PUMA strives to protect its user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee 100% the security or confidentiality of any information that you provide to us or that is otherwise disclosed by you online. We recommend that you take additional measures to protect yourself and your information, such as installing anti-virus software, closing browsers after use, keeping confidential your log-in credentials and passwords.

### CHILDRENS' PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect or solicit information online from children under 13 and we do not specifically target children under 13 in our marketing materials or other advertising.

### SHARING INFORMATION 

We may provide your information to our affiliates and subsidiaries, as well as to our partners, vendors, distributors, and suppliers, some of which may be outside the United States. We may transfer your information to certain service providers in order to conduct our business operations. For example, service providers may handle web hosting, credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We may also share your information as is necessary to complete a transaction or provide a product, service, or feature that you have requested. These serve providers will only use your information for the purpose of carrying out the services provided to PUMA and are required to keep all such information confidential. We may disclose information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property or safety. We may share information to prevent illegal uses of PUMA's products and services or violations of the [_Terms of Use_](https://us.puma.com/en/us/terms-and-conditions/TERMS_AND_CONDITIONS.html "Terms of Use"), or to defend ourselves against third-party claims. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation.

Your information may be transferred to a third party as a part of our business assets in a sale of a part or all of PUMA. If this should happen, notice will be provided via the website or other appropriate form of communication.

You may also choose to share certain information. When you join or use certain services, you agree to publicly share a basic amount of information, which may include your username, city location, and profile picture. In order to participate in certain features, you may have to adjust your privacy settings and share additional information. You may also choose to share your activity on other platforms, such as Instagram, Facebook and Twitter. Please read the privacy policies of those platforms, because your PUMA activity published on those platforms will no longer be governed by this Privacy Policy.

### DATA TRANSFER

Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the United States, and allow PUMA to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES

For your convenience and to improve the usage of our website we insert links to third party websites, for which this Privacy Policy does not apply. This includes links from partners that may use PUMA’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement or sell PUMA products. These third party websites may have their own separate privacy policies and PUMA is not responsible or liable for the content and activities of third parties. Any use of third party websites is entirely at your own risk. Please note that third party sites may use cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

### OPT-OUT, DELETE OR MODIFY INFORMATION

You may cancel your account, or opt-out of receiving e-mail messages from PUMA at any time. You can also modify or delete your account profile within certain PUMA services through your account.

To unsubscribe and stop receiving communications from PUMA, you can change your account settings or follow the instructions enclosed within the email, text message, notification or other promotional message or communication. If you have unsubscribed from any PUMA communications, due to production schedules, you may receive communications already in production. PUMA may keep information and content in our backup files and archives.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or comments relating to our website and/or the Privacy Policy, please email us at customerservice@puma.com or write to us: 

**PUMA**  
Attn: Privacy Officer 10 Lyberty Way  
Westford, MA, USA 01886

You may also contact us via telephone at [_1-888-565-PUMA (7862)_](tel:1-888-565-7862)

### TERMS OF USE

Your use of our products and services, and any disputes arising from them, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the [_Terms of Use_](https://us.puma.com/en/us/terms-and-conditions/TERMS_AND_CONDITIONS.html "Terms and Conditions"). Please visit our [_Terms of Use_](https://us.puma.com/en/us/terms-and-conditions/TERMS_AND_CONDITIONS.html "Terms and Conditions"), which explains other terms governing the use of this website, as well as our products and services.

Revised February, 2018
